const useHelpQA = () => {
  const qa = [
    {
      question:
        "What are the mandatory documents needed to list my restaurant on Food Villa?",
      answer: `
      - Copies of the below documents are mandatory 
      - FSSAI License OR FSSAI Acknowledgement
      - Pan Card book
      - Menu
      `,
    },
    {
      question:
        "After I submit all documents, how long will it take for my restaurant to go live on Food Villa?",
      answer:
        "After all mandatory documents have been received and verified it takes upto 7-10 working days for the onboarding to be completed and make your restaurant live on the platform.",
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is this one time Onboarding fees? Do I have to pay for it while registering?",
      answer:
        "This is a one-time fee charged towards the system & admin costs incurred during the onboarding process. It is deducted from the weekly payouts after you start receiving orders from Food Villa.",
    },
    {
      question: "How much commission will I be charged by Food Villa?",
      answer:
        "The commission charges vary for different cities. You will be able to see the commission applicable for you once the preliminary onboarding details have been filled.",
    },
    {
      question:
        "I don't have an FSSAI licence for my restaurant. Can it still be onboarded?",
      answer:
        "FSSAI licence is a mandatory requirement according to the government's policies. However, if you are yet to receive the licence at the time of onboarding, you can proceed with the acknowledgement number which you will have received from FSSAI for your registration.",
    },
    {
      question: "Will Hungerr be accountable for quality/quantity?",
      answer:
        "Quantity and quality of the food is the restaurants' responsibility. However in case of issues with the quality or quantity, kindly submit your feedback and we will pass it on to the restaurant.",
    },
    {
      question: "Do you charge for delivery?",
      answer:
        "Delivery fee varies from city to city and is applicable if order value is below a certain amount. Additionally, certain restaurants might have fixed delivery fees. Delivery fee (if any) is specified on the 'Review Order' page. ",
    },
    {
      question: "Is single order from many restaurants possible?",
      answer:
        "We currently do not support this functionality. However, you can place orders for individual items from different restaurants.",
    },
    {
      question: "Is there a minimum order value?",
      answer:
        "We have no minimum order value and you can order for any amount. ",
    },
    {
      question: "How long do you take to deliver?",
      answer:
        "Standard delivery times vary by the location selected and prevailing conditions. Once you select your location, an estimated delivery time is mentioned for each restaurant.",
    },
    {
      question: "Do you support bulk orders?",
      answer:
        "In order to provide all customers with a great selection and to ensure on time delivery of your meal, we reserve the right to limit the quantities depending on supply.",
    },
    {
      question: "Can I order in advance?",
      answer:
        "We currently do not support this functionality. All our orders are placed and executed on-demand.",
    },
    {
      question: "Do you support bulk orders?",
      answer:
        "In order to provide all customers with a great selection and to ensure on time delivery of your meal, we reserve the right to limit the quantities depending on supply.",
    },
    {
      question: "Do you support bulk orders?",
      answer:
        "In order to provide all customers with a great selection and to ensure on time delivery of your meal, we reserve the right to limit the quantities depending on supply.",
    },
  ];

  return qa;
};

export default useHelpQA;
